<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>E-Zhen Tan</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on E-Zhen Tan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>My name is E-Zhen Tan. I am a Year 2 undergraduate at the Singapore University of Social Sciences, currently pursuing a Bachelor of Sciences in Business Analytics.
My portfolio of prior school projects are linked here and in the tab, GitHub-Portfolio, above.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experential Learning Journey to Yangon, Myanmar</title>
      <link>/2019/09/03/oel310-reflection/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/09/03/oel310-reflection/</guid>
      <description>Abstract Duration of trip: 3-9 March 2019
This trip was organised for students to see how the workings of companies in Yangon, Myanmar. The reflection below is my insights from this week-long trip.
 Reflection As this was my first time in Myanmar, the trip was incredibly eye-opening. After hearing from various industry professionals about the achievements that the businesses have achieved and challenges that they are facing, my impression of working in Myanmar has changed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resume/</guid>
      <description>Updated: 2019-09-03
My resume is linked here.
Education  Singapore University of Social Sciences [Jul 2018 - Jul 2022 (expected)]  Bachelor of Science in Business Analytics CGPA 3.52/5.0  Jurong Junior College [Feb 2016 - Dec 2017]  GCE “A” Levels    Work Experience  Writers@Work Enrichment  English Tuition Centre for Primary and Secondary levels Teaching Assistant and Part-Time Teacher Reponsibilities include:  Teaching a regular P4Write class of 3 students from end May 2019 to end September 2019 Marking and grading scripts, ranging from P2 to APW (Secondary 3 and 4 students)   List 1  List 1a List 1b  List 2 List 3  List 3a List 3b  List 3(bi)    Singapore University of Social Sciences | Bachelor of Science in Business Analytics | Table Cell 1 .</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>