<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>E-Zhen Tan</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on E-Zhen Tan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>14 Data Science Projects</title>
      <link>/2020/09/24/14-data-science-projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2020/09/24/14-data-science-projects/</guid>
      <description>body { text-align: justify; font-size: 16px; }  ## Last edited on 2020-09-26 This post serves as a documentation of 14 Data Science projects I am committing to complete. Why am I doing this? Recently, I came across a video by Thomas Frank (from College Info Geek) about the 1% Rule, and it really got me thinking. In essence, the 1% rule states that with every new project or work, there should be an improvement of 1%.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GitHub Commands</title>
      <link>/2019/10/15/github-commands/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/10/15/github-commands/</guid>
      <description>This guide is what I have learnt from building my GitHub portfolio. It also serves as a reminder for me when I need to refer to the codes again.
Step 0: Install Git in Terminal (if you have not done so) Whether you have Git already in your command shell can be easily verified with one command. Run git in your shell. If it says command not found, then you can go ahead and install Git.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blog</title>
      <link>/post/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/</guid>
      <description>Blogposts:
Experiential Learning to Yangon, Myanmar</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resume/</guid>
      <description>Updated: 2020-09-16
My resume can be downloaded here.
Key details Availability for Internship I am available for a full-time internship position from January - June 2021 (6-month / 24-week internship).
Skills    Python R Tableau (Intermediate) IBM SPSS Modeler HTML (basic) SAS Forecast Studio (basic)     Work Experience  Jewel Paymentech
Data Science Intern
 Evaluated the accuracy of 3 trained classifiers by calculating the percentage of false positives Trained an auto-encoder to find top 1% of outliers Language used: Python   NOV 2019 - JAN 2020   Writers@Work Enrichment</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experiential Learning Journey to Yangon, Myanmar</title>
      <link>/2019/03/10/oel310-reflection/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/03/10/oel310-reflection/</guid>
      <description>Abstract Duration of trip: 3-9 March 2019
Course code: OEL310
Author: E-Zhen Tan
This trip was organised for students to see how the workings of companies in Yangon, Myanmar. The reflection below is my insights from this week-long trip.
Reflection As this was my first time in Myanmar, the trip was incredibly eye-opening. After hearing from various industry professionals about the achievements that the businesses have achieved and challenges that they are facing, my impression of working in Myanmar has changed.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>